foreign
a mild acid such as acetic acid in the
solution of sodium thiosite this doesn't
seem to be such a good idea
is masking coming back experts say that
a Chicago television news crew reporting
on a string of robberies ended up
getting robbed themselves after they
were accosted at gunpoint by three armed
men wearing ski masks
Hawaiian Electric
in pre-market trading in New York after
the utility released a statement their
power lines were de-energized for more
than six hours in Lahaina when the
afternoon fire broke out on August 8th
Gates and other investors are betting
cardoma systems can reduce carbon
dioxide in the air by chopping down and
burying trees if only Uncle Sam would
get on housing experts blame the
shortage of low-cost housing on two
primary factors the cost of land and the
expense of borrowing money to build High
lumber prices are a problem too
in an interview published by the
president's office on Sunday evening
zielinski said that he would be willing
to hold elections despite the ongoing
martial law amid the war so long as the
U.S and EU bankroll the voting process
as in pay for it
you've read the headlines you've seen
the tweets now get close and personal to
the doom and squalor of downtown San
Francisco the tour will start at City
Hall and continue through mid-market the
tenderloin and Union Square we will view
the open-air drug markets the abandoned
Tech offices the outposts of the
non-profit industrial complex and the
deserted department stores discover the
policy choices that made America's
wealthiest city the nation's Innovative
leader of housing addiction mental
health and unrepentant crime crisis how
many regular people Square Joe's on
their way to work and they'll stop hang
out with me try this drug for the first
time and then leave their life literally
not not leave from that moment on
they're just out here with us total
walking distance 1.5 miles sneakers
advised
renewable energy invest record-breaking
358 billion in the first half of 2023
solar was the key driver with a total of
239 billion dollars invested in large
and small-scale solar energy systems
[Music]
would a massive shade between Earth and
the Sun help slow climate change so the
most Exotic Solutions to climate change
are the
Viggo engineering but a Hawaiian
cosmologist has an even more far out
Idea Place a 372 Thousand Mile wide sun
shade Tethered to a captured asteroid
between Earth and the Sun to reduce the
amount of solar radiation reaching our
planet by 1.7 percent
he readily admits that this concept
would require millions of dollars
investment in just preliminary
engineering studies to see if it is
hospitalizations for foreign objects and
rectums are on the rise researchers
found an increase in hospital visits for
rectal foreign items rising from 1.2 per
100 000 persons in 2012 to 1.9 in 2021
in April the visual Journal of emergency
surgery reported that a man had to be
rushed into emergency surgery after
getting a can of deodorant stuck in his
butt foreign
[Music]
1984.
when the year came and the prophecy
didn't thoughtful Americans sang softly
and praise of themselves
the roots of liberal democracy had held
wherever else the terror had happened we
at least had not been visited by
orwellian nightmares
some measure of consented so you have to
to bring in an element this
getting people to consent what is
happening to them but we had forgotten
that alongside Orwell's dark vision
there was another slightly older
slightly less well-known equally
chilling vision
Aldous huxley's Brave New World
precisely it is that we are in process
of developing a whole series of
techniques
which will enable the controlling oligar
have always existed and presumably
always will exist uh two
dead people actually to love their
servitude
contrary to Common belief even among the
educated Huxley and Orwell did not
prophecy the same thing
Orwell warns we will be overcome by an
extremely imposed oppression
but in huxley's Vision no big brother is
required to deprive people of their
autonomy maturity and history this is my
better as you probably noticed it's a
pod
yeah
inside is pretty much just my bed and
then I've also been keeping my clothes
back here I kind of have some storage
right there and underneath so it pretty
much holds almost
um kind of all my possessions have I do
not own that much it's a little small
and it is probably not for people who
are claustrophobic
but what I kind of really enjoy about it
is that I'm now paying about 508 dollars
a month in rent and that's after uh
considering the cost of construction so
for me it really has been working out
as he saw it people will come to love
their oppression
to adore the technologies that undo
their capacities to think
[Music]
30 years ago and they build a Brave New
World which is essentially the account
of a society making use
of all the
but in order to stand at that population
to Iron Out by inconvenient human
differences to create so to say
produced to models of human beings
arranged in some kind of a scientific
caste system
what Orwell feared were those who had
banned books
against a nationwide backdrop of book
bans and censorship campaigns Iowa
educators are turning to chat GPT to
decide which titles should be removed
from school library shelves the
resulting strategy involved compiling a
master list of commonly challenged books
then utilizing AI software to supposedly
provide textual analysis for each one
flagged books were then removed from
Mason City's 7 to 12th grade Library
collections
titles included Alice Walker's the color
purple and Buzz bissinger's Friday Night
Lights
frankly we have more important things to
do than spend a lot of time trying to
figure out how to protect kids from
books Mason City's assistant
superintendent of curriculum and
instruction told Popular Science
what Huxley feared was that there would
be no reason to ban a book
for there would be no one who wanted to
read one
Americans read fewer books in 2021 than
any of the past 30 years according to
gallup's latest reading poll reading
appears to be in Decline as a favorite
way for Americans to spend free time the
new data on reading reinforces that the
popularity of reading is waning with
Americans reading three fewer books last
year than they did five years ago and
typically read for the past three
decades
the decline is not because fewer
Americans are reading it all but because
Americans who do read are reading fewer
books the decline is greatest among
subgroups that tended to be more Avid
readers particularly college graduates
Orwell feared those who would deprive us
of information
to the office of the Marion County
record that grabbed computers cell
phones and Reporting materials and rated
a journalist's home a significant update
tonight as we follow through with our
coverage of the raid on a Kansas
newspaper our investigative unit has
learned that law enforcement downloaded
copies of the newspaper's computers and
kept the data two copies of the item
seized from Marion County record and the
one law enforcement gave to the court
there are nine items listed in the one
law enforcement gave to the attorney
just eight Marion Police Justified their
raid by citing suspected identity theft
when a reporter got hold of a local
restaurant owner's driving record the
State website Marion Police Chief Gideon
Cody accuses a record reporter of
accessing illegally in his affidavit
isn't the website she used according to
Kansas Department of Revenue a day after
the raid 98 year old Joan Meyer died her
son blames her death on stress caused by
the police incursion the police get to
control what information we are allowed
to know about
then where does that take us as a
culture
White House censorship of social media
violates First Amendment rights
on March 26 2021 White House digital
director Rob Flaherty emailed Facebook
asking what sort of restrictions the
social media company was going to put on
the New York Post I'm curious NY post is
churning out articles every day about
people dying what is supposed to happen
to that from a policy perspective does
that article get a reduction
labels
asked in June the online news act or
Bill c18 requires companies like meta
and alphabet to pay Canadian news
businesses when their content ends up on
digital news intermediary platforms
Before the bill was passed meta warned
the government that the only way it
could comply was to end news
availability in Canada effectively
blocking Canadians ability to post and
view links to news sites
many news companies warned the
government that c18 would devastate in
already struggling industry
the Canadian government doubled down
[Music]
Huxley feared those who would give us so
much that we would be reduced to
passivity and egoism
the pandemic shifted our Collective
existence so that now any difficult
development compounds the Relentless
uncertainty and grief especially for
those who experienced new crises
firsthand instead of watching them
unfold from afar
the crises won't stop coming
radical acceptance is the key to coping
Orwell feared that the truth would be
concealed from us
trust and confidence in the mass media
has been on the decline in 2020 60 of
those polled told Gallup they had very
little or no trust in the mass media
back in the 70s during the Watergate
scandal that figure was almost reversed
about 70 percent of Americans had
confidence in the mass media we're in
this moment where people can really
just go just go seek out what they want
to hear and there are people who are
more than willing to tell them what they
want to hear people whatever we do are
seeing things so much to their own prism
if the president says I never said that
and we put up the video of him saying
that the public who is on his side will
still tell you he didn't say that and
insight from Texas Public Radio
a new study has made some surprising
conclusions about how Republicans and
Democrats are living in their own
separate realities the study found that
people were more likely to rate a claim
as true if it supports their political
party will we ever share a common set of
facts again
Huxley feared that the truth would be
drowned in a sea of irrelevance
lollipop
gang gang gang gang
ice cream is so good again anytime I
accidentally happen upon a tick tock
live I feel like I am watching the world
end it's a new trend that has popped up
on the Internet over the past few months
her robotic tone imitates something
called an NPC or non-playable character
in video games
ice cream yum
yum
Mommy
up one second
y'all are married if you interrupt me
again it's the latest evolution of
virtual tipping on the internet and it
sits at the intersection of gaming
culture and sex work
this is late stage societal collapse
people next let's go and put this up the
next part up here on the screen doll's
killing it right now uh in terms of uh
the New York Times what they say is she
said she has made between
two thousand and three thousand dollars
per stream across all social media
clowns accounts which include Instagram
and only fans and puts the number at
some seven thousand dollars per day
[Music]
Orwell feared that we would become a
captive culture
America has a free speech problem
for all the tolerance and Enlightenment
modern society claims Americans are
losing hold of a fundamental right as
citizens of a free country
the right to speak their minds and voice
their opinions in public without fear of
being shamed or shunned
this social silencing this depluralizing
of America has been evident for years
but dealing with its stirs yet more fear
how has this happened
in large part it's because the political
left and right are caught in a
destructive Loop of condemnation and
recrimination around cancel culture many
on the left refuse to acknowledge that
cancel culture exists at all believing
those who complain about it are offering
cover for bigots to Peddle hate speech
many on the right for all their braying
about cancel culture have embraced an
even more extreme version of
sensoriousness as a bulwark against a
rapidly changing Society but the old
lesson of think before you speak has
given way to the new lesson of speak at
your peril
Huxley feared we would become a trivial
culture preoccupied with some equivalent
of the feelies the orgy Porgy and the
centrifugal Bumble puppy
[Music]
it's a what yeah
we got that let's get some steaks
a fun thing
[Music]
foreign
as Huxley remarked in Brave New World
Revisited the Civil Libertarians and
rationalists who were ever on the alert
to oppose tyranny failed to take into
account man's most infinite appetite for
distractions
in short Orwell feared that what we hate
will ruin us
[Music]
I had to go into mental health because I
actually wanted to help people but then
here I am in my masters and it turns out
that the reason people are doing so bad
is because they're having perfectly
normal responses to their environment
that environment being poverty and
exploitation
it's like I don't want to be a therapist
because I'm supposed to tell this person
that they're not having a perfectly
normal response to their horrific
environment
it's like if I teach them to cope in
this unhealthy toxic environment that's
just keeping the system as it is
see I'm not doing too great
Huxley feared that what we love will
ruin us
the number of the predictions which were
purely fantastic when I made them 30
years ago ahead have come true or
seeming process of coming true
Meeks about which I talked seemed to be
here already and that there seems to be
a general movement
in the direction of this kind of
ultimate Revolution this this method of
control but by which a people can be
made to enjoy a state of affairs which
by any decent standard they ought not to
enjoy
the enjoyment of of servitude
welcome to your future
a digitally interdependent
hyper-connected networked world
throw off the tethers of ordinary
reality and join the digitized
multitudes ruled by global e-governance
with your very own New World citizen of
the people's Federated Republic of the
great Democratic United Global States
incorporated chip card
[Music]
just one chip is now a key to every
relevant database you are in on Earth
we're taking identification to a
technocratic level Beyond Aldous
huxley's wildest dreams and George
Orwell's nightmares one chip linked to
your unique citizen number connects to
all of your relevant societal business
including your passport your driver's
license and all Federation required
licenses titles and registrations your
car home and medical insurance all of
your medical records including your
mandatory annual psychological
evaluation your DNA profile and your
prescriptions your voter registration
and history and your bank account and
digital Universal basic income credits
but that's not all your blockchain
protected New World citizenship also
gives you a digital footprint everywhere
you go on the web from online news
sources to all of your social media
accounts authenticating you online to
ensure a safe peaceful and secure
Society where no one can offend anyone
else because no one can side
continuous real-time 24 7 tracking and
tracing will ensure a truly peaceful
digital Utopia for all
no more fear of identity theft or
forgetting those pesky passwords as your
digital citizen Mark will be
biometrically verified through your
fingerprints Iris scan EEG voice print
I'm sorry Dave and facial map from Cairo
to Rome to engelstadt to Paris to
Washington to Estonia and Astana
from Ocean to Ocean to Ocean to heck all
of the oceans being a digital resident
offers you a new concept of freedom to
be a global citizen under your
borderless digital New World Order may
be incompatible with faith in the actual
definition of freedom databases wholly
owned and operated by The People's
Federated Republic of the great
Democratic United World States
incorporated and their subsidiaries your
digital citizenship is legally binding
and data may be shared with third
parties listed in subsection
187-c.2 without your Express knowledge
or consent these terms and conditions
are subject to change at any time which
is fine because they are 8 642 pages
long and we know no one is reading the
fine print travel aloud only in
pre-approved chip validated Mega region
and not including core or Reserve
sustainable development zones as
designated by the United Nations
convention on biological diversity
online behaviors deem negative or
harmful or subject to Ubi Digital Credit
deduction without notice up to including
account termination see user agreement
for further details
our smart grid Network touches every
corner of the globe it's one digital new
and your chip is your portal to it so
apply today to authenticate and secure
your digital citizenship
because if you didn't do anything wrong
you shouldn't have anything to hide
and in this Brave New World and in this
Brave New World
you won't be able to
foreign
[Music]